孩子 千万不要低估命运的力量
Kids, never underestimate the power of destiny.
因为只要你对命运还有期待
Because when you least expect it, the littlest thing
哪怕微不足道的事情也能 给你生活带来 意想不到的变化
can cause a ripple effect that changes your life.
象我当年去芝加哥
Take for instance my trip to Chicago.
那个保安有点咸猪手
That security guard was a little bit handsy.
搞笑 她只是碰了下我
That's funny. She barely touched me.
23号登机口  快点
Uh, Gate 23. Come on.
如果我们错过了这趟班机 我永远不会原谅自己的
If we miss this flight, I will never forgive myself.
这趟班机为什么如此重要?
Why was this flight so important?
让我们回到几个月前 那是06年秋天
Let's back up a few months to the fall of 2006.
我刚刚卖掉第一份建筑设计图纸
I had just sold my first building design and become
并且成为了我们 公司历史上最年轻的经理
the youngest project manager in my firm's history.
瞬时  我成为众猎头公司的目标
Suddenly I was being headhunted.
一家公司甚至考虑 让我管理他们纽约办事处
One firm was even considering me to run their entire New York office.
他们安排我参加最后一道面试
They were flying me in for a final interview
在他们的芝加哥总部
at their corporate headquarters in Chicago.
这是一生中的少有的机会
It was the opportunity of a lifetime.
这会决定我的命运
It was my destiny.
但是有一个问题
There was just one problem.
等等 还有两个人
Hi, wait, two more.
对不起 你们迟到太久了 我已经关上登机门了
Sorry, you're too late, I already shut the doors.
能不能通融通融
Well, I'm sure if we pull real hard we can open them.
我也希望你们能进去 门一旦关上 就没有办法了
Hmm, I wish it worked like that, but see, once I close those doors, that's it.
每人能够在下到登机舱
Nobody else is allowed down that jet-way.
除了这个人
Except for that guy.
求求你了 如果 我说如果我错过这趟航班
Please, if-if I miss this flight,
我就错过我梦寐以求 的工作面试机会
I'll miss the chance to interview for my dream job.
对不起 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
他梦寐以求的工作! 难道你没有过梦寐以求的工作?
His dream job! Didn't you ever have a dream job?
你还是小女孩的时候 有一些东西 让你就是想去做
Something from when you were a little girl, that was all you wanted to do?
我的意思是 肯定是这样的 你晚上从不睡觉
I mean, for God's sakes, I'm sure you didn't go to bed at night
做做梦成为
dreaming about being a...
我的意思是
I mean, uh...
这是个不错的工作
This is a cool job.
求你了 我必须上这趟飞机
Please, I have to be on this flight.
我看看我能做什么
I'll see what I can do.
但是目前看起来不妙
But it doesn't look good.
谢谢
Thanks.
你的制服真漂亮
Your uniforms are pretty.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www  YYETS  com
Transcript : Raceman Subtitles : Willow's Team
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第十五集
翻译：     billyling   校对：      雨亦奇
www.forom.com
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
好的
Okay.
他们还没有关登机门 你们还有一线机会
They haven't armed the doors yet, so you still have a chance.
现在已经联系上机长了 他们会再跟我们联系
It's up to the captain now and they're calling us back.
太好了 请尽快告诉 我们如果你有信的话
Great, please let us know soon as you hear anything.
为了避免再次出现类是情况 我们建议你们
Sure, and for the future, we recommend you arrive
提前一个半小时到机场
at the airport an hour and a half before your flight,
而不是  晚一分钟才到
not, you know, one minute after.
平时 我总是十分守时的
Normally, I'm incredibly responsible.
我今早去了趟法院 然后等待判决
I just had to go to court this morning and get sentenced.
我不是犯罪分子  一点关系都没有
Not that I'm a criminal or anything.
他只是跳了下地铁十字转门
Yeah, he just jumped a subway turnstile.
你看起来对交通规则理解有很多问题
You seem to have a lot of problems with the rules of travel.
你好?
Hello?
噢 太好了
Oh, that is great news.
我妈妈打来的 她找到她丢的耳环了
It's my mom-- she found her missing earring.
坐吧 我一有消息就叫你们
Have a seat. I'll call you when I hear something.
在那找到的?
Where was it?
这件对她来说比等回话好多了
That thing better have call waiting.
你能给公司打个电话 解释下发生了什么吗?
Could you just call the firm and explain what happened?
那可是3个人
It's down to three people
并且我知道他们 今天就要做出最后决定
and I know they need to make their decision today.
我感觉我没露面 会给我带来竞争上的劣势
I sort of feel my not showing up might put me at a disadvantage.
我太笨了
I'm so stupid.
我为什么要去跳转门?
Why did I have to jump that turnstile?
别这样怪自己了
Hey, don't be so hard on yourself.
难道整件事不该怪巴尼?
And isn't this whole thing really Barney's fault?
她说的对
She had a point.
从某种意义来说是巴尼的错
It was kind of Barney's fault.
让我们再回到几个月前
Let's back up a few months.
马修 脚趾怎么样了?
Oh, Marshall, how's the broken toe?
天啊 疼死我了
Oh,  man, it kills.
要来点阿司匹林吗 宝贝?
You want some aspirin, baby?
你知道我不喜欢止疼药的
You know I don't believe in pain killers.
你第一次骨折
Wow, your first broken bone.
打破了你从不"骨折"的历史
Kind of kills your whole "Unbreakable" theory.
马修曾经一度 以为他是不会受伤的
Marshall used to think he was indestructible.
打住 我之前从来没有骨折过
Well, it added up. I've never broken anything.
从来没有生过病  而且当我需要时
I've never been sick, and when I need to,
我能获得无穷的力量
I can summon incredible strength.
泰德 告诉她 关于沉重的门的故事
Ted, tell her the story of the really heavy door.
确实有个很重的门
There was a really heavy door.
他打开了
He opened it.
还是一只手
On one pull.
你现在肯定不行了 明天你也不能去跑步了
Well, you must be really bummed, you're not gonna be able to run tomorrow.
是啊 太郁闷了
Yeah. It sucks,
所有的马拉松训练都成无用功了
all that work I put in training for the marathon was a total waste.
马拉松训练?
Training for a marathon.
怎么了?
What?
马拉松根本不需要训练 跑就得了
You don't need to train for a marathon. You just run it.
你开玩笑?
You're kidding, right?
本来就是 我想什么时候跑马拉松都行
Not at all. I could run a marathon anytime I wanted to.
那明天 你认为你醒来 起床后
So like tomorrow, you think you could wake up, roll out of bed,
就直接去参加纽约马拉松赛?
and just run the New York City Marathon?
没问题
Absolutely.
巴尼  我们说的可是42公里
Barney, we're talking about 42 kilometers.
好的  我接着说
Thanks, Canada. I'll take it from here.
巴尼 看起来有26迈远
Barney, it's like 26 miles.
我来告诉你们怎么跑马拉松
Here's how you run a marathon.
第一步 起跑
Step one, you start running.
然后就 没有了
There is no step two.
你懂啥啊 证明给我们看
Okay, you know what? Prove it.
拿我的号去跑
Take my number and run in my place.
我赌50美元你根本跑不完比赛
I will bet you 50 bucks you don't even finish the race.
50美元?
50 bucks?
要是我赢了
Gee,  Grandpa, if I win,
我可能可以买个冰淇淋
maybe I can buy myself an ice-cream cone.
赌 10,000美元
Make it $10,000.
你赌不赌?你输了也要给我50美元
You have a gambling problem. You'll bet me 50.
那就不赌了
Fine, then no bet.
好吧 50美元就50美元
Okay, $50.
第二天一早  马拉松开始
The next morning, as the marathon began,
我们就都把注意力放在马修的电脑上
we were focused on Marshall's computer.
每一个选手都有个追踪芯片 你可以在网上跟着他们
Each runner gets a tracking chip so you can follow them online,
当他们过了检查 巴尼的鞋上就会有我的芯片信号
see when they pass certain checkpoints. Barney's got mine in his shoe.
他开跑了
Ooh, he's starting!
看起来很好
This ought to be good.
噢
Wow.
他已经过了第二个检查站了
He's already passing the second checkpoint.
这个追踪器太好了
This tracking thing is amazing.
我们结婚了以后都得有一个
When we get married, you're getting one of these.
看他的时间 太快了
Wow. Look at his time. It's pretty impressive.
他肯定在做假
He's gotta be cheating, okay.
他知道我们在看他
He knew we'd check.
他会不惜余力来赢这次赌
Yeah, he'll do anything to win a bet.
记得那次他和我 打赌让那男的唱"饿狼传说"
Remember that time he bet me that Men at Work sang "Hungry Like the Wolf,"
他们不唱  然后他花钱让他们唱
and when he found out that they didn't, he tried to hire them to?
看起来 "巴尼"应该要过Queensboro桥了
Well, it looks like, "Barney" should be coming over the Queensboro Bridge
一个小时后会到达第一大道
and up First Avenue within the next hour or so. But...
但是  这不可能是他
there is no way that that's really him.
真的是他啊
It's really him.
嘿 那是我的
Hey! That's mine.
也好 你最好是逃跑
Yeah, you'd better run!
怎么样啊 失败者?
- What up, non-finishers? - Wow.
太出色了 巴尼 不是吗?
- Very impressive, Barney. - Right?
我本来应该在提前半个小时的
Yeah, my time would have been like a half an hour better,
跑到7迈的时候 遇到热水瓶了我们抄近道
but I met this total hottie on Mile Seven. We took a quick detour
我们的迷你马拉松 就在内森的后面
and had our own mini marathon behind a Nathan's.
我赢了
I won.
我不觉得任何人 是赌局的赢家
I'm  not sure anyone in that story is a winner.
我的50美元呢?
So where's my 50 bucks?
好吧
All right.
我承认 你赢了
I got to admit, you earned this.
他们怎么没做个50美元的硬币
Huh? Can't believe they haven't made a coin for this yet.
好了 我回家了
Anyway, I'm heading home.
也许还要去趟健身房
Might go hit the gym.
等等 跟你说 所有马拉松参赛者都可以
Oh, hey, just so you know, uh, all marathon runners get
今天免费坐地铁
to use the subway for free today.
我真的应该去看看"兔女郎"
Wow. You know I really should check out this "subway."
听说了那么多
Heard so much about it.
看着我 佩服吧
Wow. Look at me. Slumming it.
也许  我会拿一周出来
Maybe I'll make a weekend out of it
今晚嘛 就找个一般的了
and I'll call my bridge and tunnel girl tonight.
你今晚和新泽西的女孩约会?
You're dating a girl from New Jersey?
当然不
No.
巴尼真做到了
So Barney did it.
他确实完成了马拉松
He actually finished the marathon.
但过了一会 我接到了一个有趣的电话
But a little while later... I got an interesting phone call.
你好? 泰德 我 巴尼
- Hello? - Ted, it's Barney.
我需要你来地铁站接我
Listen to me, I need you to come and pick me up on the subway.
怎么了 你说什么呢?
What, what are you talking about?
我就坐在这 正在想我的好事
I was sitting here, totally minding my own business.
胜利者
Finisher.
你知道我再说啥
Yeah, you know what I mean.
86号街到了
86th street.
我脚动不了了
My legs don't work.
我已经在地铁上 坐了整整两个来回了
I've already ridden the subway twice end to end.
我没有发现有所好转
I've seen where it turns around.
泰德  你一定不想看到地铁来回转
Ted, you don't ever want to see where the subway turns around.
巴尼的脚动不了了
Barney's legs won't work.
他下不了地铁了
He's riding the subway from end to end
因为他身体上已经已经不能下车了
because he physically can't get off the train.
这是我花的最好的50美元
Best 50 bucks I ever spent.
听我说 泰德
Listen to me, Ted.
你快过来我等不及了 我在6号车的4号车厢
I'm going to lose you any second. I'm on the fourth car of the six train
从布鲁克斯区的帕港往南开
heading south from Pelham Bay Park in the Bronx.
在86号街站等我 半个小时内能到吗?
Meet me at the 86th Street station in, like, half an hour?
好的  我这就去
All right. I'll be right there.
呆在那别动
Stay where you are.
泰德  泰德
Ted, Ted.
你不会连他位置都不让
Oh, come on. You're not even going to give up your seat for him?
对不起  我不能让
I'm sorry. I can't.
脑子进水了
Douche.
巴尼? 泰德!
- Barney?! - Ted!
嘿 站住
Hey!
不要...
No...!
明白了吗?如果巴尼不参加马拉松
See? If Barney never tried to run the marathon,
你就不会跳转门
you never would have jumped that turnstile,
你今天也不会去法院
you wouldn't have had that court date today,
我们就可以赶上航班
and we would have made this flight.
你说的对
You're right.
所有事都归罪于他
Everything can be traced back to him.
象当时圣诞的轻率一样
Like that rash we all got at Christmas.
好吧 我看看怎么样了
All right, I have to see what's going on.
- 那我能帮你订到两个 - 真的吗? 那太好了!
- So I was able to get you two seats. - Really? That's great!
不 没跟你说 我再跟我妈说Blue Man组合的门票
No, no, not you. I'm talking to my mom about Blue Man Group.
妈 我再给你打过来好吗?
Ma, can I call you back?
我们的航班怎么样? 我们能登机了吗?
Okay, what about our flight? Can we get on?
我还在等...
I'm still waiting for... Huh.
看起来你们的航班已经起飞了
Looks like your flight left already.
什么?不 不 不... 我今天必须得到芝加哥
What? No, n-n-n-no, n-no. I have to be in Chicago today.
那机长就根本没有给你打过来?
Well, he never even called you back?
这才是典型飞行员 工作时绝不回电
Well, it's typical pilot. They don't call you back at work
他们打过来除非你们
and they don't call you back after you spend two nights with them
在奥兰多 Radisson 和他们渡过两晚
at a Radisson in Orlando.
事情有了转机 正好有另外一趟航班
It turned out there was one other flight that would just barely get me
能让我及时 去芝加哥参加工作面试
to Chicago on time for my job interview,
但是登机口在机场的另外一头
but it was all the way on the other side of the airport.
是哪个航空公司的航班
What was the name of the airline again?
好像是R'Us 航空公司
I think it was something like Flights R' Us.
"R"是在后面吗? (同音:我们赶不上了)
Was the "R" backwards?
老天 希望不是
God, I hope not.
快啊 好手推车
- Geez. - Stupid smart carts.
更像笨推车
More like dumb carts.
如果我们错过航班 一定都是巴尼的过错
If we miss this flight, it's all Barney's fault.
巴尼决不可能在马拉松跑第一
You know, Barney never would have run the marathon in the first place
如果马修脚趾没有骨折的话 那难道不是?
- if Marshall hadn't broken his toe. - Yeah, so?
那你觉得是我的过错?
What, you think this is my fault?
对马修来说  参加马拉松 的想法的产生在四月
For Marshall, the initial idea to run the marathon came way back in April.
我的内裤穿起来有点紧了
My pants are starting to feel a little tight.
没关系  我喜欢你的小肚腩
Oh, that's okay. I love that cute little belly.
我不能再这样下去了
I cannot allow this.
怎么了啊?
What?
我要去参加纽约马拉松赛
I am going to run the New York City Marathon.
碳水化合物摄入很重要
"It is important to load up on carbohydrates
在长跑2-4个小时之前
two to four hours before a big run.
早餐一个百吉饼 一个香蕉
Try a breakfast of a bagel, a banana,
麦片 草莓 和一些橙汁
oatmeal, strawberries and some orange juice."
过来吃吧 马修这些食物 都按照书上说的弄的
Here you go, Marshmallow. Just like the book said.
但从现在起 我要 象职业选手一样吃早餐
Yeah, but from now on, I'm eating all of my breakfast runner-style.
液体消化要快得多
Liquids are digested faster.
换句话说 没有能量流失
That way, no energy is wasted,
这些都是为了比赛
and it's all about the run.
别忘了给自己很多鼓励
"Don't forget to give yourself plenty of positive reinforcement."
这会是你最好的比赛
This is gonna be your best run yet.
你会实现你所有的梦想
You're going to accomplish all of your goals.
你是一个来自未来的机器人
You are a robot sent from the future
为了赢得马拉松
to win the marathon!
你是...马修
You are... Marshall.
你是...马修!
You are Marshall! Yeah!
身上一些地方也许会出现发炎或者水泡
"Chafing or blisters can occur in a number of areas,
出现的地方包括脚 腋窝 甚至乳头
including the feet, armpits, or even the nipples.
试试在这些有反应的地方用些油霜
Try using some petroleum jelly on the affected areas."
噢  糟了!
Oh, gosh!
兄弟 你是一个所向披靡的选手
Dude, you are a terrific runner.
明天你将参加并且完成纽约马拉松
Tomorrow you're gonna run and finish the New York City Marathon!
你是最棒的
You're the best.
你看起来太好了
You look good.
没人比你更强
Nobody does it better than you.
马修?我的天!
Marshall? Oh, my God!
这样说 是 确实是你的错
So, yes, it was your fault.
我的意思是 如果你中午不突然去我公寓的话
I mean, if you don't show up at the apartment in the middle of the day,
马修脚趾就不会骨折 巴尼也不会带他去跑
Marshall doesn't break his toe, Barney doesn't run in his place,
我也不会去跳转门和法院
I don't jump the turnstile and get a court date,
我们就有足够的时间来赶上飞机
and we make our flight in plenty of time!
我也不会在机场摔到还咬伤舌头
And I don't fall down and bite my tongue at the airport.
这真的不是我的错
That really wasn't my fault.
如果不是因为 莉莉我也不会撞见马修
I wouldn't have walked in on Marshall if it weren't for Lily.
你想想...
Hey,  think about it.
那怎么了?
Hey, what's going on here?
不知道 看起来 他们象在露营什么的
Oh, looks like they're camping out for something.
对啊 可为什么啊?
Yeah, but for what?
不知道  经常有突击队迷 或者星战迷来通宵排队
I don't know. Usually there's a Stormtrooper or Klingon in line
看来这是原因了
to give you some indication.
"年度婚纱甩卖"
"Annual wedding dress blowout.
设计样品试穿打9折
Designer sample dresses up to 90% off.
明天早上8点开门
Doors open tomorrow, 8:00 a.m."
你相信这些真能省钱?
Oh, my God. Can you believe what some nut bags will do to save a few bucks?
我们一定要露营
We have to camp out.
- 你说真的吗? - 你不懂
- Are you serious? - You don't understand.
太划算得甩卖了 我从来没有遇到过
This is an amazing sale. I've heard about it before,
我从来不知道哪有这些
but I never knew where it was.
我们将来个婚纱露宿 一定很有趣...
We'll have a wedding dress campout. It'll be fun.
我不能去 我有事
I can't go. I've got this thing.
- 什么事? - 房事
- What thing? - A penis.
就是这了
- This is the place. - Oh, wow.
Badgley Mischka! Melissa Sweet! (服装品牌)
Badgley Mischka! Melissa Sweet!
Vera Wang! (华裔婚纱设计师)
Vera Wang!
你知道我们为什么在这?
Oh, Robin, do you have any idea what you guys stumbled onto here?
你说了Wang (发音错了)
You said wang.
它让我想到了1998年排队买Lilith Fair的票 (音乐会)
Oh, this reminds me of the ticket line to Lilith Fair, 1998.
没有 胭脂鱼 (骂人的话)
Only fewer mullets.
你应该感到满足 你是纽约 仅有的10分之1最疯狂的新娘
You should feel good. You're only, like, the tenth craziest bride in New York.
真舒服
Ooh, this is comfy.
我们肯定能睡着
We might actually be able to sleep.
真让人讨厌
That's kind of annoying.
我确定呆会就有人出来把它关了
Well, I'm sure somebody will be out here to turn it off any minute.
我觉得我不能忍受了
I don't think I can take this.
每次它声音一变小
Every time it turns off, I think,
它也许就不会再响了
oh, maybe it won't turn on again,
但是它又响了
but then it does.
为什么会这样 罗宾?
Why does it, Robin?
为什么它总响个不停
Why does it keep turning on?
会好的 甜心 为什么
It's gonna be okay, sweetie. Why...
为什么我们不能 来玩个游戏? 怎么样?
Why  don't we make a game out of it, okay?
我们跟着它一起唱歌吧?
Why don't we sing along?
如果我们能做到的话
If we get through this,
我发誓我一定会过另一种生活
I swear I'm gonna live my life differently.
我只想对我父母 说再说一次我爱他们
I just want to tell my parents I love them one more time.
早上好 女士们
Morning, ladies.
就是他 他就是车主! 滚开...
- It's him. It's the car guy! - Get out of here!
第二天早晨 罗宾累得不想回布鲁克林
The next morning, Robin was too tired to go all the way back to Brooklyn,
而我又在上班
so while I was at work,
她就去我公寓呆上两个小时
she went to crash at my apartment for a couple hours,
然后
and that's when...
没人比你更强
Nobody does it better than you.
马修?!天啊!
Marshall?! Oh, my God!
如果莉莉不唆使我一起去婚纱店
So if Lily hadn't dragged me down to the wedding dress store,
我们能赶上第一趟飞机
we would have made the first flight.
谢天谢地 门还开着 我们赶上了
Oh, thank God. The doors are still open. We made it.
你好 求求你了 我们一定得上这趟班机
Hi. Please. We really need to get on this flight.
噢 天啊!
Oh, my God!
你是城市新闻1台的播音员
You're that reporter from Metro News 1.
是 是 我就是
Yes, yes, I am.
你居然能认出我
I can't believe you recognized me.
你编的大比萨饼的故事? 你能说说...
- You did that story on the giant pizzas? - Would you check to see
- 还有空位? - 等会 先生
- if you have any more seats? - One moment, sir.
那些比萨饼是真的?不是吧?
Were those pizzas real? Come on, were they?
罗宾...等会 泰德
- Robin... - One second, Ted.
很多人问我同样的问题
Um, you know, a lot of people ask me that.
事实是 比萨饼是真的
The truth is, the pizzas were real.
- 馅是假的 图像处理过的 - 我就知道是这样的
- Calzones. Trick photography. - I knew it!
遇到一个粉丝太高兴了
God, it is so nice to meet a fan!
我也很开心成为你的粉丝 如果你能帮我们
And I would be a fan of your work if you could get us
在下趟航班留两个座位的话
two seats on that next flight.
乘务员刚刚检查完位置
Well, the, uh, flight attendants are just finishing up their final seat count.
让我看看能发现什么
Let me see what I can find out.
如果能帮忙赶上的话 我就能做一个关于我命运的激情演讲?
Would it help if I got on and gave an impassioned speech about my destiny?
我觉得情况可能不好
I think it might hurt.
真是一场噩梦
This is such a nightmare.
好 统一意见? 回到莉莉想露营
Okay, so we agree? This goes back to Lily wanting to camp out
因为婚纱...
for a wedding dress?
不
No.
等等 回去更远些
Wait. It goes back further.
记得我们为什么在东边吃热狗?
Remember why we were eating hot dogs on the East Side?
1939年?!
1939?!
这是枚1939年造的便士!
This penny's from 1939!
有67年历史的便士
A 67-year-old penny.
你能想到这枚便士 是二次大战时造的吗?
Do you realize this penny was minted during World War II?
就是我的祖父 这个也不让他感兴趣
Oh, so was my grandfather, but that doesn't make him interesting.
我懂一些硬币知识
Look,  I know a little something about coins,
这个宝贝对于收藏家来说还是值钱的
and this baby is worth something to a collector.
- 不 它啥也不是 - 不 它肯定值钱!
- No, it's not. - Yes, it is!
你知道什么?我带你去吃饭
You know what? I'm gonna take you out to dinner
用这个便士换来的钱
with the money I get for this little guy.
这就是我做得
And that's exactly what I did.
你真走运还有这么个 地方把这个换成15美元
You're lucky there's still a place that serves anything for a dollar fifty.
这可是它本身价值的150倍啊
Hey, that's 150 times its original value.
这顿饭只花了14.9美元
Actually, the meal was only $1.49.
1984造的
1984.
50年之内了 我们又可以吃了
Hey, in 50 years, we can get dinner again.
你太过分了
How dare you.
嘿 那怎么了?
Hey, what's going on?
不知道 看起来 他们象在露营什么的
I don't know. Looks like they're camping out for something.
对啊 可为什么啊?
Yeah, but for what?
是我
It was me.
我开始了这一切
I started this.
如果我不捡那一便士
If I hadn't picked up that penny,
我们就不会沿路吃热狗
we wouldn't have gone to get hot dogs all the way across town.
我们就不会看到婚纱店
And we wouldn't have seen that wedding dress store,
莉莉也不会想在那露营
Lily wouldn't have wanted to camp out there,
我也不会第二天去你公寓休息
and I wouldn't have needed a nap at your apartment the next day.
马修脚趾也不会骨折
Marshall wouldn't have broken his toe.
巴尼也不会去跑马拉松
Barney wouldn't have run the marathon.
我也不会去跳转门
I wouldn't have jumped that turnstile,
被捕 还去法院
gotten arrested, had that court date...
我们就能赶上航班了
And we would have made our flight.
我认为我们 不能再追回到更远了
I don't think we can go back any further than that
除非你知道谁丢的那一便士
unless you know who dropped the penny.
我希望是我
I wish I did.
反正那人已经得到了惩罚了
Though that person's already been punished enough,
丢了那么值钱的一便士
losing a sweet penny like that.
先生?
Uh, sir?
请你告诉我点好消息
Oh, please tell me you have some good news.
恐怕不行
Uh, I'm afraid not.
这趟航班没有空位了
There are no extra seats on the plane.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
算了吧  还是谢谢你尽力了
All, right, well, thanks for trying.
我不敢相信
I can't believe this.
晚了 都完了
That's it, it's over.
泰德 别这样
Ted, come on.
你命运就是今天到不了芝加哥
Your destiny just wasn't to make it to Chicago today.
如果哪个公司真要你的话 他们会重新安排的
Anyway, if that firm really wants you, they'll reschedule.
但这再也没有发生过
But that's not what happened.
他们没有重新安排
They didn't reschedule.
他们雇了别人
They hired someone else.
三个月 这一切都过去了
And as it turned out, three months later,
那个家伙的纽约工作 也结束了又回到了芝加哥
that guy ended up having to relocate to Chicago.
孩子们 这就是命运的趣事
Kids, funny thing about destiny--
我曾经认为 我一定会得到这份工作
I thought I was destined to get that job.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
我的命运是呆在纽约
My destiny was to stay in New York.
因为如果我没有
Because if I hadn't,
我就不会遇见你们的妈妈
I never would have met your mother.